[Music]
[音乐]
hi welcome to this screencast on the set
嗨，欢迎来到现场的这个截屏视频
garbage collector i'm pallidum i'm an
垃圾收集器，我是苍白球，我是
engineer in the java platform group at
工程师在Java平台组
oracle working on garbage collection
甲骨文致力于垃圾收集
so I'll start by giving an overview of
因此，我将首先概述
what said UC is and how it works we'll
UC是什么以及它如何工作，我们将
have a look at some performance numbers
看看一些性能数字
and I'll end by showing you how to get
最后，我将向您展示如何获得
started using CGC
开始使用CGC
so said you see is a new garbage
所以说你看到是一个新的垃圾
collector which is available it has an
可用的收集器有一个
experimental feature in starting with
开始的实验功能
JDK 11 we described said you see as
我们描述的JDK 11表示您认为
scalable low latency garbage collector
可扩展的低延迟垃圾收集器
and to get a little bit better
并变得更好一点
understanding of what we mean with that
了解我们的意思
let's have a look at the goals we had in
让我们来看看我们的目标
mind when designing this so when we say
在设计时要注意，所以当我们说
it's a low latency GC we mean that GC
这是一个低延迟的GC，我们的意思是GC
post times never exceed 10 milliseconds
后次不会超过10毫秒
and when we say it's scalable we mean
当我们说它是可扩展的时，我们的意思是
that this GC can handle heaps ranging
该GC可以处理堆范围
from small to very large we're very
从小到大，我们非常
large means multi terabytes here are
大意味着这里有数TB
some of the key features of said you see
您说的一些主要特征
at its core said UC is a concurrent
从本质上说，UC是并发的
garbage collector which means that all
垃圾收集器意味着所有
the heavy lifting down by a GC is done
GC完成了繁重的工作
while your threads continue to execute
当您的线程继续执行时
so things like marking compaction and
所以像标记压实
all other expensive operations are
所有其他昂贵的操作
handled without stopping the Java
处理不停止Java
threads said UC currently has a single
线程说UC目前只有一个
generation under the hood it uses load
在引擎盖下产生负荷
barriers and caller pointers as the main
障碍和呼叫者指针为主要对象
techniques to achieve concurrency it's
实现并发的技术
region based which means that the heap
基于区域的表示堆
is divided into many smaller regions and
分为许多更小的区域和
said you see can choose to only compact
说你看到只能选择紧凑
a subset of those typically those that
通常是那些
contain the most garbage and it's also
包含最多的垃圾，而且
Numa wear so when a job object or
Numa穿着，所以当工作对象或
javathread allocates an object that
javathread分配一个对象
object will be allocated in memory that
对象将在内存中分配的
is local to the CPU
对于CPU是本地的
keep property of said you see is that
保持财产的说，你看到的是
most times do not increase with the heap
大多数时候不随堆增加
size or lives its size so it doesn't
大小或实际大小，因此不会
matter if you have a one gig heap or a
无论您有一个演出堆还是一个
one terabyte II post times will not be
1 TB II发布时间将不会
affected by that
受此影响
so let's have a quick look at what
让我们快速看一下
happens when said you see is collecting
当你说你正在收集时发生
garbage so this picture shows you what a
垃圾，这张照片告诉你什么
GC cycle looks like inside you see and
GC周期看起来像您看到的内部
the different places it goes through and
它经历的不同地方
blue arrows here pointing downwards
这里的蓝色箭头指向下方
represent these forces and the gray
代表这些力量和灰色
arrows pointing sideways represent
指向侧面的箭头表示
concurrent phases so let me walk you
并行阶段，所以让我带你
through a GC cycle and briefly describe
通过GC周期和简要说明
what's going on in each of these phases
这些阶段的每个阶段都发生了什么
so the cycle starts with the mark start
所以循环从标记开始
pause this is where thread stacks are
暂停，这是线程堆栈所在的位置
scan to find object pointers these
扫描以找到这些对象的指针
object pointers are also known as routes
对象指针也称为路由
we then continue with the concurrent
然后我们继续并发
mark phase and this is where this is an
标记阶段，这是一个
expensive operation where the GC walks
GC运行的昂贵操作
entire object graph and marking the
整个对象图并标记
objects it finds as live we then come to
它发现的物体是真实的，然后我们来到
the market and pause this is a
市场和暂停，这是一个
synchronization point to coordinate the
同步点以协调
end of the marking phase and once this
标记阶段结束，一旦完成
has been reached the GC now has complete
已经到达GC现在已经完成
lioness information so it knows which
母狮信息，因此它知道哪个
objects are live and which are garbage
对象是活动的，是垃圾
and we now transition to the concurrent
现在我们过渡到并发
prepare for relocate phase
准备搬迁阶段
in this phase number of things happens
在这个阶段发生了很多事情
but I'll just highlight two of the more
但我只强调其中两个
interesting parts here which is
这里有趣的部分是
reference processing and relocation set
参考处理和重定位集
selection so reference processing is
选择，因此参考处理是
where the GC takes care of soft week and
GC负责软周的工作，
phantom references and finalization and
幻像引用和定稿以及
the relocation set selection is where
重定位集选择在哪里
the GC figures out what parts of the
GC会找出
heap needs to be compacted to free up
堆需要压缩以释放
memory we then transition to the
记忆，然后我们过渡到
relocation phase this starts with the
搬迁阶段始于
relocate start pools where thread stacks
将启动池移至线程堆栈所在的位置
are scanned to handle roots pointing
进行扫描以处理根源指向
into the location set and we then come
进入位置集，然后我们来
to the concurrent relocate face and this
到并发搬迁的面孔，这
is where the heavy work of compacting
是压实的繁重工作
the heap happens and by compacting the
堆发生并通过压缩
heap the GC will free up large
堆GC将释放大空间
contiguous chunks of memory and make
连续的内存块和
that memory available for new
该内存可用于新
allocations
分配
and that completes the Jesus icon I want
这样就完成了我想要的耶稣圣像
to point out here that the Jesus idols
在这里指出耶稣的偶像
that we have here will be very short as
我们在这里会很短
I mentioned before the reason why I said
我之前提到我为什么说
you can keep these forces below 10
你可以把这些力量低于10
milliseconds is because no heavy lifting
毫秒是因为没有沉重的负担
is done while the jaw threats are
在下颚威胁时完成
stopped all that is down here is
停止了这里所有的一切
essentially scanning or threat stacks
本质上是扫描或威胁堆栈
and this typically can be done well
这通常可以很好地完成
within the limits of 10 milliseconds
在10毫秒内
okay so let's have a look at some
好吧，让我们来看一些
performance numbers this shows you the
性能数字可以向您显示
score us from spectator be comparing
从观众那里给我们打分，进行比较
said you see with a parallel GC and G
说你看到用并行GC和G
one spec jb b is a well-known java
一个规范jb b是著名的java
benchmark which produces two scores max
产生最大两个分数的基准
j ups and critical j ups
暴跌和关键暴跌
max j UPS is a row throughput score
最大j UPS是行吞吐量得分
while critical j ups is a
而关键的起伏是
latency-sensitive score showing the
潜伏期敏感分数显示
throughput achieved under an SLA and as
根据SLA和
we can see on this benchmark you said
我们可以在这个基准上看到你说的
you see is on par with a parallel GC and
您看到的与并行GC相当，并且
G one when it comes to row throughput
行吞吐量为G一
and said you see it's well ahead of the
说你看到了
other collectors when it comes to the
其他收藏家
latency sensitive score and this is of
潜伏期敏感分数，这是
course thanks to the low cost times here
当然要感谢这里的低成本时间
we have the GC post times for the same
我们有相同的GC发布时间
benchmark the light blue bars here show
基准显示此处显示的浅蓝色条
the average post time for each GC and
每个GC的平均发布时间，以及
the black part shows the worst post time
黑色部分显示最差的发布时间
and then we have some of the higher
然后我们有一些较高
percentiles in between the post times
发布时间之间的百分位
for CDC barely registers here so to get
CDC几乎没有在这里注册，因此
a better sense of what's going on lets
更好地了解正在发生的事情
me switch the time axis to use a
我切换时间轴以使用
logarithmic scale
对数刻度
like that and now we can see that the
这样，现在我们可以看到
average post time for CDC is roughly one
CDC的平均发布时间约为1
millisecond with the worst forced time
最差的强制时间毫秒
of around two milliseconds and this is
大约两毫秒，这是
well below sadducees goal of never
远低于萨杜迪的永不实现目标
having pauses exceeding 10 milliseconds
具有停顿超过10毫秒
in contrast we can see that the other
相反，我们可以看到另一个
collectors have average post times
收藏家的平均发帖时间
between 150 and 200 milliseconds with
在150到200毫秒之间
the worst post times on the order of 300
最差的发布时间约为300
to 500 milliseconds
到500毫秒
so let's have a look at what you need to
让我们来看看您需要
know to get started using said you see
知道开始使用说你明白
first of all there is a new JVM option
首先有一个新的JVM选项
to enable said you see and that's called
使说你看到，这叫做
you said you see since this is still an
您说您看到了，因为这仍然是
experimental feature you also need to
实验功能，您还需要
supply the option to unlock extra rental
提供解锁额外的租赁选项
features and a few words on tuning so
功能和关于调整的几句话
first of all we've been working hard to
首先我们一直在努力
make said you see easy to do and to
说你觉得容易做
avoid exposing a lot of GC tuning
避免暴露很多GC调整
options
选项
the main tuning option is setting the
主要的调整选项是设置
max heap size and since said you see is
最大堆大小，因为说你看到的是
a concurrent collector you need to
您需要的并发收集器
select a max heap size that well first
选择最合适的最大堆大小
of all can accommodate the live set of
所有可以容纳现场的
your application but you also need to
你的应用程序，但你还需要
have enough Headroom in the heap to
堆中有足够的空间
allow allocations to be serviced
允许分配服务
while the G's is running how much
G跑了多少
Headroom you need very much depends on
您需要的净空高度取决于
the allocation rate and the live set
分配率和现场布置
size of your application and in general
您的应用程序和一般大小
the more memory you give to said you see
你给我的记忆越多，你看到的
the better but at the same time you
更好，但同时
don't want to waste memory so it's all
不想浪费内存，仅此而已
about finding a balance between memory
关于在记忆之间找到平衡
usage and how often the GC needs to run
使用情况以及GC需要运行的频率
the second tuner option that you might
您可能会选择的第二个调谐器选项
want to look at is setting the number of
想看的是设置数量
concurrent GC threads said UC has
并发GC线程表示UC具有
heuristics to select this number and
启发式选择此数字，然后
this usually works well but depending on
这通常效果很好，但是取决于
what type of workload you're running you
您正在运行哪种类型的工作负载
might want to adjust this this option
可能要调整此选项
basically it says how much CPU time
基本上说多少CPU时间
you're willing to give to the GC and if
你愿意给GC，如果
you give it too much then the GC will
你给它太多，那么GC会
steal too much CPU time from your
从您的服务器上窃取过多的CPU时间
application but on the other hand if
申请，但另一方面
this number is too low then the GC might
此数字太低，则GC可能
not be able to keep up and that's
无法跟上，那就是
basically it when it comes to tuning
基本上是调音
there are a few other options but these
还有其他一些选择，但是这些
are the two main options you want to
是您要选择的两个主要选项
look at when tuning set you see
看一下调音台
to enable logging I'd recommend you use
启用日志记录，我建议您使用
one of the following two options X log
以下两个选项之一X日志
GC will give you basic logging with a
GC将为您提供基本的日志记录
single line printed per GC this line
每行GC每行打印一行
will only provide high-level information
仅提供高级信息
such as why the GC was triggered and
例如触发GC的原因，以及
what the heap size or heap usage was
堆大小或堆使用量是多少
before and after the GC X log G C star
GC X log GC星号之前和之后
will give you a more detailed logging
将为您提供更详细的日志记录
this can be useful when tuning or if you
这在调优或如果您
just want more information on what's
只想了解更多信息
going on under the hood
引擎盖下继续
sadducees currently only available on
目前仅在
linux x86 64 bit additional platforms
linux x86 64位其他平台
might be supported in the future if
如果将来可能会支持
there is enough demand for them
对他们有足够的需求
so to summarize said you see offers low
所以总结说你看到报价低
latency with the post time staying below
延迟时间低于发布时间
10 milliseconds its scalable so you can
10毫秒的可扩展性，因此您可以
have a huge heap without affecting the
有一大堆而不影响
GC post times it's easy to tune and it's
GC发布时间很容易调整，而且
available in JDK 11 you can find
您可以在JDK 11中找到
additional information on that you see
您看到的其他信息
on the open JDK wiki
在开放的JDK Wiki上
download JDK 11 today at Oracle comm /
立即从Oracle comm下载JDK 11 /
Java download and if you're interested
Java下载，如果您有兴趣
in participating in open JDK development
参与开放的JDK开发
go to open JDK java.net or you can
打开JDK java.net或可以
follow us on Twitter for news and
在Twitter上关注我们以获取新闻和
updates thanks for watching
更新感谢您的观看
[Music]
[音乐]